gtv.com 2014-11-08

# Privacy Policy | GTV

GTV recognizes that the users of GTV.com value their privacy and we take your privacy seriously. This Privacy Policy (as defined below) explains our privacy practices, including what types of information we collect from you and how we may use it, our rights to share and disclose such information to third parties and how you can review and modify information that you provide to us and your preferences regarding our use or disclosure of such information.

This is the privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) for www.GTV.com (the “Site”). The Site is provided by GTV Corporation and its affiliates (“GTV”, “we” or “us”). Please review our Terms of Use Agreement which governs your use of the Site. Any capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning given in the Terms of Use Agreement.

This Privacy Policy will remain in full force and effect, even if your use of or participation in the Site or any particular service, feature, function or promotional activity offered through the Site terminates, expires, ceases, is suspended or deactivated for any reason. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not participate in the Site or any features, activities or services offered through the Site.

This Privacy Policy applies regardless of the Device you use to access the Site and whether you are accessing the Site as a registered user or otherwise. This Privacy Policy governs only the Information collected by us on the Site and does not cover any other information collected in any other manner or collected by any other entity, unless specifically stated. We may combine your Information with other information we collect from other sources, such as information received from our affiliated companies, marketing companies or Advertisers and, if we do so, our use of the resulting combined Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

You may choose to provide certain information to us when you use the Site. When we use the term “Personal Information” we mean any information that we collect on the Site that would allow someone to identify you or contact you, such as your full name, address, e-mail address or telephone number. When we use the term “Additional Information”, we mean any information that we collect on the Site other than Personal Information, like your musical preferences, etc. (Personal Information and Additional Information will be collectively referred to as “Information”). By visiting, accessing or otherwise using the Site, you affirmatively consent to our collection and use of Information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

    1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT 
      * A. User Registration. If you elect to become a registered user of the Site, we will require you to provide a username and password (together, your “User ID”), along with certain Personal Information including your email address and date of birth. In addition, you may be given the option (but are not required) to provide Additional Information, such as your gender, country and mobile phone number.
      * B. Site Features, Functions and Communications. The Site may provide you with access to certain features or functions, such as interactive and community features, message boards, ratings and profile pages. To participate in these features and functions, you may be asked to provide certain Information about you in order to personalize and/or allow you to use these features and functions. For example, in order to personalize your user profile on the Site, you will have the option to provide a profile image, your city, state and country and a short description of yourself. At times, you may be presented with the opportunity to sign up to receive newsletters, email communications, or other communications from us in order for us to provide up-to-date information about the Site, and to publicize and promote certain content, products and services offered by us or our business partners. When there is a separate sign-up for newsletters, we may ask for your contact information such as name and email address, and, sometimes, demographic and profile information.
      * C. Contests, Sweepstakes and Surveys. To participate in certain Site-related contests, sweepstakes and surveys, there may be a separate registration process which may require the submission of both Personal Information and Additional Information (including your full name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, demographic or profile information, etc.). We will use the Information you provide for the purpose of conducting the promotion (for example, to contact you if you have won). You may also have the opportunity to opt-in to receive special Promotions or offers from our Advertisers as a result of your use of the Site.
      * D. Information Collected Through Automatic Data Collection. Our Site includes features that automatically collect Additional Information regarding your visits to the Site to assist us in keeping track of your preferences, create a more tailored user experience and better serve your particular interests and needs.

The Site and/or third parties may use “cookies,” (which are small data files containing information about you that is stored on your hard drive), “embedded scripts”, and other similar tracking technologies (collectively, “Tracking Technologies”) to collect Additional Information automatically as you interact with the Site. Some cookies are used to make login to our Site easier (such as by remembering your User ID). Cookies also enable us to track your interaction with the Site and target your interests to enhance your Site experience (e.g., for tracking your sessions and use of the playbar, what videos you have in your playbar, etc.). We may also use Tracking Technologies to collect “clickstream” data, such as the domain name of the service providing you with Internet access, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your browser type and version, operating system and platform, the average time spent on our Site, pages viewed, content searched for, access times and other relevant statistics, and assign unique identifiers to the Device you use to access the Site for the same purposes. Your Personal Information is not collected as part of this process. However, we may associate the information obtained through these Tracking Technologies with your Personal Information so we can better customize your Site experience and provide tailored advertisements and Promotions related to your specific interests. By visiting the Site, whether as a registered user or otherwise, you acknowledge, understand and hereby agree that you are giving us your consent to track your activities and your use of the Site as described in this Privacy Policy.

This Site may also use a variety of third party advertising networks, data exchanges, traffic measurement service providers, marketing analytics service providers and other third parties (collectively, “Third Party Advertising Service Providers”) to, for example, serve advertisements on the Site, facilitate targeting of advertisements and/or measure and analyze advertising effectiveness and/or traffic on the Site. Such services may enable us to display advertisements based on your visits to the Site and other websites you have visited. Targeting services enable us to, among other things, help deliver advertisements or other content to you for products and services that you might be interested in, to prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times and to conduct research regarding the usefulness of certain advertisements to you.

      1. HOW WE USE INFORMATION

We may use your Personal Information for many purposes, including, without limitation, the following:

      * Contacting you regarding the administration of any features or functions of the Site you have registered to use;
      * Sending you marketing and promotional e-mails;
      * Allowing you to participate in the community features of the Site;
      * Responding to your questions or other requests;
      * Tailoring your experience on the Site and/or otherwise customizing what you see when you visit the Site;
      * Saving your User ID or other Personal Information (so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site); and
      * For other purposes disclosed at the time you provide us with the Personal Information.
      * In addition, we may use the Additional Information for many purposes, including, without limitation, the following:
      * Tracking your return visits to the Site;
      * For research purposes, for marketing/promotional purposes and/or to provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients;
      * Accumulating and reporting aggregate, statistical information in connection with the Site and user activity;
      * Determining which features and services users like best to help us operate the Site, enhance and improve our services and the Site and display advertising and marketing information;
      * Tailoring your experience on the Site and/or otherwise customizing what you see when you visit the Site;
      * Saving certain Additional Information for use on your return visits to the Site;
      * For the uses described for “Personal Information” above; and
      * For other purposes disclosed at the time you provide us with the Additional Information.
    1. OPTING-OUT OF CERTAIN USES OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND OTHER INFORMATION 
      * A. Marketing and Promotional Communications. At times, you may be presented with the option of whether to receive certain marketing and promotional communications from us and others that we think will be of interest to you. Recipients of such communications can unsubscribe by either following the specific instructions included in such communications or you may “opt-out” of receiving marketing and promotional e-mails from us at any time by sending an email to us at privacy-admin@GTV.com detailing your privacy request. Please note, however, that in order to keep you informed about the operation of our Site and related services, we may always send you emails and announcements that are needed for the proper functioning and administration of our Site, including for the purposes described in Section 2 above, in connection with your use of the Site. We may also have features that allow you to submit information, questions or feedback to us. In those instances, we may retain your emails and other information you submit to us for our internal purposes, and to help us to serve you better.
      * B. Use of Additional Information Collected by Tracking Technologies. If you would like to learn more about how Third Party Advertising Service Providers collect Additional Information about your interaction with the Site or find out how you can opt out from allowing these Third Party Advertising Service Providers to gather this information or use it to display targeted ads, please visit http://www.freewheel.tv/privacy.html and http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp. Opting-out of, deleting or disabling Third Party Advertising Service Providers’ Tracking Technologies does not mean that you will no longer receive online ads. Opting-out to, deleting or disabling Third Party Advertising Service Providers’ Tracking Technologies only means that such ads will no longer be tailored to your specific viewing habits or interests, but you will continue to see ads on this Site.
    2. SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION AND OTHER INFORMATION 
      * A. General Disclosure. Generally, we do not sell, rent, lease or disclose your Personal Information to third parties, except if you consent to such disclosure or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to use and/or sell any aggregated data we collect in connection with your use of the Site, including for the purposes described in Section 2 above. We may disclose Personal Information to our affiliated companies for marketing and/or administrative purposes. You can choose to opt-out of certain such uses as described in Section 3 above. We may share Additional Information with third parties, but we do not disclose Personal Information to them except as described in this Privacy Policy.
      * B. Co-Branded Services and Features. The Site may offer co-branded services and features, such as events and Promotions provided by us and/or our affiliated companies or other third party partners, and that may be hosted on the Site and/or our co-branded partner’s website. We may share your Personal Information with such co-branded partners and your voluntary use of or participation in a co-branded service or feature means that you opt-in and give your affirmative consent to both the Site and our co-branded partners to collect any information provided in connection with the specific co-branded feature or service and to use such information for the fulfillment of the feature or service and for marketing or administrative purposes. The co-branded partner will be identified on the co-branded feature or service, along with the co-branded partner’s privacy policy. If you wish to opt-out of a co-branded partner’s future use of your Personal Information for marketing purposes, you will need to contact the co-branded partner directly and the use of such information by co-branded partner is subject to co-branded partner’s privacy policy.
      * C. Disclosure of Certain Information in User Postings Intended to Be Disclosed. Certain Personal Information associated with a User Posting may be intended for disclosure, such as your username. We will disclose any such Personal Information in connection with the display of, and other services relating to, such User Posting and by submitting a User Posting on our Site you affirmatively consent to the distribution of your Personal Information as described herein.
      * D. Site Service Providers. We also have the right to disclose your Personal Information and other information to third parties for the purpose of administering and maintaining the Site’s services, features, functions and operations. We will refer to these third parties as “Site service providers”. We use Site service providers to efficiently provide the full range of content, activities, services, features and functions we bring you and we disclose your Information to Site service providers for the purpose of providing services to us. These Site service providers may temporarily store some information on their servers, but they may only use your Personal Information to provide GTV with a specific service and not for any other purpose.
      * E. Other Third Parties. Other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not share your Personal Information with other third parties, apart from those acting as our agents in providing our Site to you, and which agree to use it only for that purpose and to keep the information secure and confidential. Also, please be aware that our affiliated companies, including all their respective business units, subsidiaries, affiliates and sites, entities into which our companies may be merged, or entities to which any of our assets, products, sites or operations may be transferred, may obtain from us and be able to use your Personal Information.
      * F. Additional Disclosures. There may be instances when GTV may access or disclose Information without providing you a choice in the following circumstances: (1) to protect or defend the legal rights or property of GTV, our affiliated companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (2) to protect the safety and security of our Site and users; (3) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; (4) if we believe your actions violate the Terms of Use Agreement, this Privacy Policy, any Rules and/or Additional Terms; or (5) to comply with law or legal process. In addition, if GTV sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of all or a material part of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, GTV may transfer your Personal Information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.
    3. USER CHOICE AND ACCESS 
      * By accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy, you expressly choose to receive certain communications from us and certain third parties, and you expressly agree to the privacy practices described herein. You may change your privacy preferences (e.g., choose to cease receiving certain communications or ask us not to share your Personal Information with a particular third party) by sending an email to legal@GTV.com detailing your privacy request. Other privacy preferences (e.g., hiding your user profile or deactivating your user account) may be made by modifying your account settings on the Site. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, GTV will get your permission before we use the Personal Information you provide to us in a way that is inconsistent with the purpose for which it was submitted or share your Personal Information with third parties that are not affiliated with GTV. If you ask GTV to stop using your Personal Information, we will honor that request while retaining a record of any Personal Information as necessary to comply with applicable federal, state or local law. You always have the right to access and correct the Personal Information you have provided and generally you may review, update or delete certain Information collected by the Site at any time by accessing your account as described in this Section 5.
    4. DATA COLLECTION FROM CHILDREN We do not knowingly collect personal information from U.S. children under 13 without appropriate parental notice and consent. Please visit http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/consumer/tech/tec08.shtm for information from the Federal Trade Commission about protecting children’s privacy online.
    5. SECURITY While no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure from intrusion, we maintain commercially reasonable physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your Personal Information. However, regardless of our efforts and the Device you use to access the Site, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications over an unsecured transmission. We also limit access to the Site by our own employees, contractors, Site service providers and those individuals who are authorized for the proper handling of such information. We request that our third party contractors and Site service providers follow similar standards of security and confidentiality.
    6. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS If you are a resident of the State of California, we provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options such as your right to opt-out (which we may sometimes refer to as “unsubscribe”) or opt-in for use of your Personal Information by third parties (such as Advertisers) for marketing purposes. Therefore, pursuant to the California Civil Code, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that received your Personal Information for marketing purposes during the preceding year. If you are a California resident and wish to request information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices, please send a request by email to our Privacy Administrator at legal@GTV.com or by postal mail to GTV Corporation, c/o Privacy Administrator, 318 S. Cochran Avenue, Los Angeles, CA 90036.All requests must be labeled “California Privacy Rights” on the email subject line or envelope or post card. For all requests, please clearly state that the request is related to “California Privacy Rights”, include your name, street address, city, state, zip code and e-mail address (your street address is optional if you wish to receive a response to your request via email) and indicate your preference on how our response to your request should be sent (email or postal mail). We will not accept requests via the telephone or by fax. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.
    7. LINKS The Site may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies. The Site may also feature advertisements from other third parties. GTV is not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites or other services operated by third parties that are linked to or integrated with the Site or for the privacy practices of third party Internet advertising companies. Once you leave this Site via such a link, access a third party application (such as widgets) or click on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site to determine, among other things, how they will handle any personally identifiable or other information that they may collect from you.
    8. PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES From time to time we may modify this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our Information collection and use practices, the features of the Site, or technology, and such modifications shall be effective upon posting. Your continued use of the Site after we post a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. It is therefore important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes. If we materially change our practices regarding collection or use of your Personal Information, your Personal Information will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change.
    9. ACCURACY It is your responsibility to give us current, complete, truthful and accurate information, including Personal Information, and to keep such information up to date. We cannot and will not be responsible for any problems or liability that may arise if you do not give us accurate, truthful or complete information or Personal Information or you fail to update such information or Personal Information. We will reject and delete any entry that we believe in good faith to be false, fraudulent or inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.
    10. CONTACT US  
If you have any questions about our privacy practices or any of the terms or conditions of this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at: Email: privacy@GTV.com  
OR  
Mail: GTV LLC  
Attn: Privacy Matters  
318 S. Cochran Avenue  
Los Angeles, CA
    11. SOLE STATEMENT This document is the sole statement of the Site’s Privacy Policy and no summary, restatement or other version thereof, or other privacy statement or policy, in any form, including, without limitation, machine-generated, is valid.

This Privacy Policy was last modified on the date indicated above and is effective immediately.

Copyright © 2014 GTV Corporation
